https://www.penguin.co.uk/company/about-us/notices/privacy-policy.html

Features
Find your next read...
100 must-read classic books
Does fiction need speech marks?
Industry Commitment to Professional Behaviour
At Penguin Random House, we value our readers, authors, colleagues and partners just as much as the stories we publish. Below is a brief Q&A summary of what you need to know about our Privacy Policy. You can read the full policy here.
What information do you collect about me?
The following points relate to all users of our websites:
If you visit our websites, we will collect certain information about how you'll use them - for example, information about your device, your IP address, geographical location, your browser type, how you navigated to us (e.g. through a search engine). This information may be collected by a third-party analytics service or by third parties using cookies, which are active on our website. You can read our full Cookies Policy here.
If you contact us, we will collect any information contained in any correspondance.
If you upload or post to any account on our website, we also collect that information.
If you follow any of our social media accounts, in accordance with the platform's own Privacy Policy, we may collect information about the other people that you follow or interact with.
How do you use my data?
Firstly, we'll only use your data either as part of our services to you, with your consent (where we request it) or within our legitimate business interests.
This may be in providing you with personalised content, understanding the performance of our websites or if we have a legal obligation to use your data. We may also share your data with social media platforms, so that they may also select and serve relevant advertising for you (e.g. through Facebook - you can disable Facebook's cookie via your own Facebook settings).
We'll always take into account any potential impact that our data use may have on you.
Who do you share my information with?
Third parties we may share your personal information with include those who we work with to deliver our business operations (e.g. our web developers, digital advertisers) or any members of the Penguin Random House group.
How do you look after my information and how long do you keep it for?
We look for opportunities to minimise the amount of personal information we hold about you. We use technological and operational security measures to protect your information against any unauthorised access or unlawful use - such as ensuring the security of our offices, appropriate password protection and encryption, maintaining a rigorous data protection policy and limiting access to your personal information for those in our company who need to use it.
Will you process my data outside of the EEA (European Economic Area)?
No, except when we are sharing information with one of our group companies (e.g. Penguin Random House India), using service providers based outside the EEA or if you are purchasing a product from one of our websites.
What are my rights about the information which you hold about me?
You have many rights about the information which we hold about you, including asking us to request access to the information we hold about you and to stop processing information about you.
Do you have any examples of information you may collect about me?
Yes, we have collected examples of information that we collect for our most common user groups across all of our websites. Please see the following sections of the full Privacy Policy:
For readers/purchasers
For authors
For prospective employees or freelancers
For Consumer Insight participants
Read the full privacy policy
Sign up to the Penguin Newsletter
For the latest books, recommendations, offers and more
Please enter an email.
Please enter a valid email address.
Sign Up
By signing up, I confirm that I'm over 16. To find out what personal data we collect and how we use it, please visit our Privacy Policy
Thank you for signing up to the Penguin Newsletter
Keep an eye out in your inbox.
Oops! it seems you've already subscribed to this newsletter.
View all newsletter
Subscription failed, please try again
Cookie Policy
Our Use of Cookies
We use cookies on this site to enable certain parts of the site to function and to collect information about your use of the site so that we can improve our visitors’ experience.
For more on our cookies and changing your settings click here
My Options
SAVE & CLOSE
ACCEPT ALL
Strictly Necessary
Strictly Necessary cookies enable core functionality such as security, network management, and accessibility. You may disable these by changing your browser settings, but this may affect how the website functions. See More.
Analytics
Analytics cookies help us to improve our website by collecting and reporting information on how you use it. These cookies may be set by us or by third-party providers whose services we have added to our pages. See More.
Preferences & Features
Preference and Feature cookies allow our website to remember choices you make, such as your language preferences and any customisations you make to pages on our website during your visit. See More.
Targeting / Advertising
Targeting cookies are used to make advertising messages more relevant to you and your interests. They perform functions like preventing the same content from reappearing, ensuring ads are displayed and, in some cases, selecting content based on your interests. See More.
SAVE & CLOSE
ACCEPT ALL
